I'm sure you all aspire to the genetic research department.
我相信你们都向往基因研究部门。
Why are you looking for me?
你为什么找我？
I believe
我相信
only you
只有你
i can complete this task
我能够完成这个任务
but i don't know
但我不知道
why did you delete it
你为什么删除它
An early obsession with bionics
仿生学的早期痴迷
Even memory
就连记忆
discernment
明眼
Since its establishment
成立至今
Investigator turnover is high
调查人员流动性很大
some people were killed
有些人被杀
He still suffered some injuries and retired from the second line.
他仍然受了一些伤，从二线退役。
even some people
甚至有些人
Biomimicry has long been a threat.
长期以来一直受到仿生学的威胁。
I'm thinking
我在想
if we
要是我们
Bionic memory eraser
仿生记忆橡皮擦
During the investigation
调查期间
Biomimicry could soon lose its resistance
仿生学很快就会失去抵抗力
Investigator casualties will be reduced.
调查人员的伤亡将会减少。
will never be retaliated against
永远不会受到报复
I got you.
我明白你的意思。
Become an android
成为仿生人
I completely forgot about my original obsession.
我完全忘记了我最初的执念。
and
和
At the same time you have to make them forget about their feelings.
同时你必须让他们忘记他们的感受。
Is that what you mean?
你是这个意思吗？
we can change our minds
我们可以改变主意
Maybe we are protecting humanity.
也许我们是在保护人类。
OMG
我的天啊
when they created androids
当他们创造仿生人时
What is everyone saying?
大家都怎么说
remember?
记住？
A new era is coming, remember?
新时代即将来临，还记得吗？
Then a problem arose for humans.
然后人类出现了一个问题。
They say it's a psychotropic drug.
他们说这是一种精神药物。
need to be deported away from them
需要被遣返远离他们
you're right
你说得对
all my members
我所有的成员
I have family behind me
我身后有家人
every time they sacrifice
每次他们牺牲
I have to face my parents
我必须面对父母
their wives and children
他们的妻子和孩子
I do not know what to do
我不知道该怎么办
if you say so
如果你这么说
may be selfish
可能是自私的
If you are also facing the same danger
如果你也面临同样的危险
if you let me choose
如果你让我选择
Hope my friends survive
希望我的朋友们能活下来
if
如果
we can no longer change
我们无法再改变
as an android
作为一个仿生人
If I can make you forget everything
如果我能让你忘记一切
restart
重新开始
It's also liberating for them.
这对他们来说也是一种解放。
Let's think about it carefully
我们仔细想一下
gentlemen
先生
teacher help me
老师帮助我
How many times has Teacher Huang told you this sentence?
这句话黄老师跟你说过多少遍了？
Please don't affect our business. terribly sorry.
请不要影响我们的生意。很抱歉。
no problem, no problem
没关系，没关系
you are taking drugs
你在吸毒
My wife and I are separated, please let me wait a moment.
我的妻子与我分居，请让我稍等一下。
Let's go, let's go, let's go
我们走吧，我们走吧，我们走吧
You two, don't embarrass him.
你们两个，别让他难堪。
Didn't he say he was leaving?
他不是说他走了吗？
I'm really sorry
实在抱歉
sorry.
对不起。
Don't show it to him
别给他看
maid
女佣
take it and eat it
拿走并吃掉它
Thanks
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢。
good guy
好人
Sorry for taking you so far
抱歉让你走了这么远
Take a look at my new experimental area
看看我新开的实验区
This battle of yours is still getting more intense.
你的这场战斗，还在愈演愈烈。
A famous person helped me
一位名人帮助了我
Help me, help me, help me
帮帮我，帮帮我，帮帮我
help me
帮我
I'm not an imitator. How are you doing at work?
我不是模仿者。你们工作怎么样？
Help me, help me, I run fast
帮帮我，帮帮我，我跑得很快
gentlemen
先生
take it and eat it
拿走并吃掉它
Thanks.
谢谢。
drag me away
把我拖走
go
去
What do I think of this person?
我对这个人有什么看法？
It's like we've met somewhere
就像我们在某个地方见过一样
This person is an imitator
这个人是一个模仿者
Are you sure he is?
你确定他是吗？
I feel sorry for Dr. Zhang.
我为张医生感到难过。
I'll go check the situation
我去看看情况
You should send Dr. Zhang away.
你应该把张医生送走。
OK
好的
Sorry Dr. Zhang
对不起张医生
Follow me, please
请跟我走
I can walk by myself
我可以自己走路
No need to send it to me, thank you
不用发给我，谢谢
help me
帮我
we are not
我们不是
We are not all imitators
我们并不都是模仿者
help me
帮我
Dr. Zhang
張博士
What does withdrawing an experiment mean?
撤回实验意味着什么？
no experiment
没有实验
Completed
完成的
you
你
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
I'm having a little difficulty.
我遇到了一点困难。
Difficulties that I simply cannot solve
我根本无法解决的困难
If this continues
如果再这样下去
The consequences will be serious
后果将会很严重
More than I thought
比我想象的还要多
It goes against our original intention
违背了我们的初衷
mine
我的
or yours
或者你的
what are you saying
你在说什么
Mr. Guofeng is still here
国峰君还在
Are you going to keep it a secret from me?
你打算对我保密吗？
what are you hiding
你在隐藏什么
What exactly is the purpose of this experiment?
这个实验的目的究竟是什么？
i can explain to you
我可以向你解释
Do you conduct experiments on humans?
你在人体上进行实验吗？
Do you know this?
你知道这个吗？
I am human
我是人
bitter memory
苦涩的记忆
Clear
清除
I believe the experiment was successful
我相信实验是成功的
Beneficial to the entire human society
对整个人类社会有益
Why
为什么
You mentioned this experiment at the beginning.
你一开始提到了这个实验。
Eliminate the original obsession of the bionic.
消除仿生者最初的痴迷。
and memory
和记忆
resurrect them
让他们复活
I have agreed to participate
我已同意参加
Please explain it well
请好好解释一下
I don't care what your reasons are
我不在乎你的理由是什么
i will stop you
我会阻止你
You don't know how serious the consequences will be.
你不会知道后果有多严重。
The emergence of bionics
仿生学的出现
Maybe we can learn a lesson.
也许我们可以吸取教训。
When will we wake up?
我们什么时候才能醒来？
Do you know that this experiment was successful?
你知道这个实验成功了吗？
what does it mean for humans
对人类意味着什么
what i want to do
我想做的事
Just take away the bionic's initial obsession.
只需消除仿生者最初的痴迷即可。
The experiment is over
实验结束了
terribly sorry
很抱歉
Experiment must be completed
实验必须完成
Completed
完成的
let me go tell me
让我走，告诉我
in your latest report
在您最新的报告中
There will be a successful experimental subject soon
马上就有成功的实验体了
Tell me who it is and I let her go.
告诉我是谁，我放了她。
She forgot about the experiments and lived well.
她忘记了实验，生活得很好。
produce experimental results
产生实验结果
i ruined
我毁掉了
Where did you hide that person?
你把那个人藏到哪里去了？
let go
松手
Tell me who you are, are you crazy?
告诉我你是谁，你疯了吗？
Let me go
让我走
who
谁
Wan Guofeng is
万国峰是
The manager took special leave in the morning.
经理早上请了特别假。
I'm not going home today
我今天不回家
Where did he go
他去哪了
Didn't say
没说
Is there something urgent?
有什么紧急的事情吗？
No
不
Won't you come out?
你不出来吗？
Do you want me to find it?
你想让我找到它吗？
Is Mango Peak located here?
芒果峰位于这里吗？
Not here
不在
Do you know where he went?
你知道他去了哪里吗？
I told you
我告诉你了
I have nothing to do with him
我和他没有任何关系
How do you know where he is?
你怎么知道他在哪里？
He tied up my dear friend
他绑住了我亲爱的朋友
must find him
必须找到他
He learned the art of extinguishing his initial obsession.
他学会了消除最初痴迷的技巧。
for humans
用于人类
If his plan succeeds
如果他的计划成功的话
Against bionics and humanity
反对仿生学和人类
There is great harm
有很大的危害
If anyone is more interested
如果有人更感兴趣一点
help me
帮我
please consider
请考虑
where he is most likely hiding
他最有可能藏身的地方
here we go
开始了
night
夜晚
we do it here
我们在这里做
This is
这是
your home
你家
Yes
是的
before
以前
I go on vacation every year with my family.
我每年都会和家人一起去度假。
But the place has been vacant for a long time.
但这个地方已经空置很长时间了。
You have to be patient first.
你必须首先要有耐心。
your daughter
你的女儿
OK
好的
We will be back with mom soon.
我们很快就会回到妈妈身边。
Yes, yes, my photo
是的，是的，我的照片
It’s okay, Mom, I’ll post it next time.
没关系妈妈，我下次再贴。
let's do it again
我们再来吧
I promised to come on vacation
我答应来度假
very big leader
非常大的领导者
We would be late and walking would be difficult.
我们会迟到，走路会很困难。
Dad my photo
爸爸我的照片
Hey
嘿
The signal at my house is not good, please wait.
我家信号不好，请稍等。
answer the phone
接电话
right back
右后卫
Hey
嘿
moxi mosi mabu moxi mosi
莫西莫西曼布莫西莫西
can you hear me
你能听到我吗
Wait a moment
等一下
Hey
嘿
can you hear me
你能听到我吗
please say yes
请说好
Wanbu
万部
We have something going on here
我们在这里遇到了一些情况
cannot be resolved immediately
无法立即解决
Arrival may be delayed
抵达可能会延迟
knew
知道了
be safe
注意安全
An Qiu
安秋
How did you find this place?
你是怎么找到这个地方的？
Where is Angie?
安吉在哪儿？
You went to see your wife.
你去看你的妻子了。
She told you about this place
她告诉过你这个地方
Don't let her get involved
不要让她参与进来
You get her involved.
你让她参与其中
she told me everything
她告诉了我一切
He also told me about his daughter.
他还向我讲述了他女儿的事。
Can you hear the car?
你能听到汽车的声音吗？
You have
你有
let's stop and see
让我们停下来看看
It doesn't matter
没关系
Even if I stop, I don’t know what happened
即使停止也不知道发生了什么
stop on edge
停在边缘
Let's go meet the boss first
我们先去见见老板吧
Father
父亲
i can never forgive you
我无法永远原谅你
you killed my daughter
你杀了我女儿
Ting
婷
terribly sorry
很抱歉
It's all my fault
都是我的错 婷
Why wasn't you the one who died?
为什么死的不是你？
you use imitation
你使用模仿
Develop technology to solve the original problem
开发技术来解决最初的问题
Maybe to erase my painful memories.
也许是为了抹去我痛苦的记忆。
Bioabuse experiments narrated by Yoon Jung-hong
尹正弘讲述的生物滥用实验
It may also be relevant to you
它可能也与您相关
Don't you think you are being selfish?
你不觉得你很自私吗？
Cheng Nuo
程诺
You do not understand
你不明白
this will be a great achievement
这将是一项伟大的成就
Because you've never felt real pain
因为你从未感受过真正的痛苦
I believe there are people who have the same pain as me
我相信有人和我有同样的痛苦
I have a chance to help them
我有机会帮助他们
No one wants to experience pain
没有人愿意经历痛苦
However, we cannot interfere with people's emotions at will.
但是，我们不能随意干涉人的情感。
many years ago
多年前
How many experiments have I done?
我做了多少实验？
how much effort you put in
你付出了多少努力
I want to find a way to make the pain go away
我想找到一种方法让痛苦消失
If you experiment with androids
如果你用仿生人进行实验
You can definitely achieve the effect you want
一定可以达到你想要的效果
But it erases people's memories
但却抹去了人们的记忆
We still need human experimental samples.
我们仍然需要人体实验样本。
I will provide experimental samples
我将提供实验样本
You can do any experiment on them.
你可以对它们做任何实验。
As long as I get the result
只要我得到结果
This is a great turning point that science and technology has brought to mankind.
这是科学技术给人类带来的伟大转折。
I'm not the only one
我不是唯一一个
I can still surrender to the one who lives in all the pain
我仍然可以屈服于那个生活在所有痛苦中的人
release all
全部释放
you said so much
你说了这么多
You're just running away from guilt.
你只是在逃避罪恶感。
You have contributed to the development of mankind with your sense of justice.
你们以自己的正义感为人类的发展做出了贡献。
In fact, you're only doing it for your own selfish reasons.
事实上，你这样做只是出于你自己的自私原因。
one person
一人
made a mistake
犯了一个错误
in his life
在他的一生中
I want to know if it is not allowed
我想知道是否不允许
Why
为什么
we can't forget the hurt
我们不能忘记伤害
Can't we just start over?
我们就不能重新开始吗？
I want to erase my memory and color everything
我想抹去我的记忆，给一切上色
But that regret
但那个遗憾
cause pain
引起疼痛
I'm very careful
我很小心
Don't be wrong again
别再错了
tell me
告诉我
Where is Angie?
安吉在哪儿？
tell me where ange is
告诉我安吉在哪里
OK
好的
Don't say such nice things
别说这么好听的话
if your mother was still alive
如果你母亲还活着
Don't you want to get back together with her?
你不想和她复合吗？
Do you want to live with regrets forever?
你想永远活在遗憾中吗？
What did you say?
你说什么？
you heard me
你听到我说话了
You know what?
你知道什么吗？
Does my mother's death have anything to do with you?
我母亲的死与你有什么关系吗？
Did you kill her?
你杀了她吗？
is that so
是这样吗
you can start over
你可以重新开始
but you
但是你
never allowed
永远不被允许
minister
部长
An Qiu
安秋
Anshu, are you okay?
安舒，你还好吗？
let's go
我们走吧
Anqiu Anqiu
安秋安秋
An Qiu
安秋
OK
好的
Cheng Nuo
程诺
leave me alone
请别打扰我
Angie I will help you
安吉我会帮助你
An Qiulai
安秋来
come early
早点来
you?
你？
It's okay, I'll wait outside.
没关系，我在外面等着。
Fast
快的
I am with you
我和你在一起
Too late
来不及
don't leave me
别丢下我
An Qiu
安秋
you look at me
你看着我
Let's protect it once
让我们保护一次吧
don't do that
不要那样做
You can restart
您可以重新启动
live for yourself
为自己而活
Cheng Nuo
程诺
PhD
博士
What kind of person do you want me to protect?
你想要我保护什么样的人？
anyone
任何人
You can protect who you want to protect
你可以保护你想保护的人
from now on
今后
So I got my new first obsession
所以我有了新的第一个痴迷
I didn't instill an initial obsession in you.
我没有向你灌输最初的痴迷
Rely on you
依靠你
I
我
This is an empathic ability that you develop independently.
这是你独立发展的一种共情能力。
Breaking the rules of bionics
突破仿生学的常规
body physiological structure
身体生理構造
started again
又开始了
Completely independent
完全に独立自主的
life individual
生命个体
A living individual is
活着的个体是
It's you
是你
independent
独立自主
Thanks
谢谢
How are you?
你还好吗？
you haven't changed at all
你一点也没有改变
After all, I can only give you fruit.
毕竟我只能给你水果。
Why don't you stay?
你为什么不留下来？
I leave
我离开
Be kind to everyone
对每个人都友善
i remember everything
我记得一切
your mother
你的母亲
Experiment completed
实验完成
because she noticed
因为她注意到
I get to choose who I want to protect
我可以选择我想保护的人
I told you
我告诉你了
I won't leave you
我不会丢下你
local news
本地消息
Wan Guofeng, Head of the Xiyuan City Branch of Bright Eyes
明眸西原市支部長万国峰
Suspected of conducting human experiments without permission
涉嫌未经许可进行人体实验
Abuse of humans and bionic humans
虐待人类和仿生人类
He was summarily deported and handed over to judicial authorities.
他被立即驱逐并移交给司法当局。
Private laboratories in the country were shut down.
该国的私人实验室被关闭。
Relevant departments will strengthen cooperation with Mingyu
相关部门将与明宇加强合作
Strict review of private measures against domestic counterfeiters
严格审查针对国内造假者的私人措施
and inhumane experiments
和不人道的实验
i always want to
我总是想
I am not the son she wanted.
我不是她想要的儿子。
she finally felt
她终于感觉到
for bionic products
用于仿生产品
So I did a lot of things on purpose
所以我故意做了很多事
make her angry
让她生气
and spend more time
并花更多时间
angry with her
对她生气
to the end
到最后
I didn't get a chance to apologize to her.
我没有机会向她道歉。
What I can make up for is
我能弥补的是
She is the only choice
她是唯一的选择
stop what she wants to stop
停止她想停止的事情
Protect the people you want to protect
保护你想保护的人
But the person she wants to protect
但她想要保护的人
always you
永远是你
i miss my son
我想念我的儿子
us
我们
separated for too long
分离太久
I want to go back to him
我想回到他身边
ask for his forgiveness
请求他的原谅
next to him
和他旁边
Study again and become a mother
再读书当妈妈
He may be like you
他可能和你一样
clever
聪明的
very friendly
非常友善
it's strong
它很坚固
who knows?
谁知道？
I don't know when I can see him
我不知道什么时候才能见到他
look by youself
你自己看
any scientific and technological development
任何科学技术的发展
Respect Life
尊重生命
The birth of bionic man
仿生人的诞生
This is an experiment that humans should never perform.
这是人类绝对不应该进行的实验。
Good and evil in human nature
人性的善与恶
It should not be defined by the initial obsession.
它不应该由最初的痴迷来定义。
love and hate
爱与恨
success and failure
成功与失败
Loss and redemption
失落与救赎
after everything i've been through
在我经历了一切之后
us
我们
truly understand your own heart
真正了解自己的心
We cannot expect too much from ourselves to avoid making mistakes.
我们不能对自己期望过高，以免犯错误。
But we shouldn’t run away from pain
但面对痛苦我们不应该逃避
Just face it
就是去面对它
beat it
战胜它
win it
赢得它
at last
最后
Pain nourishes our growth.
痛苦滋养我们的成长。
Know the beauty of life
认识生命之美
let us move on
让我们继续前进
believe us
相信我们
One day I will become a better version of myself
有一天我会成为更好的自己